<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Flogo - Docs and Tutorials</title>
    <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Project Flogo - Docs and Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building your first activity</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/extensions-developer/create-activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/extensions-developer/create-activity/</guid>
      <description>Adding a new activity to Flogo is quite easy and we&amp;rsquo;ve outlined the steps for you in this howto guide. This guide will walk you through the steps required to create a simple activity which can also be used in the Flogo web UI. We&amp;rsquo;ll be leveraging the flogogen scafolding CLI available via the flogo-cli repo. See below for details on installing Flogo + CLI.
Prerequisites Before you can get started with this guide you need to make sure you have the right prerequisites installed:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environment variables</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/configuration/environment-vars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/configuration/environment-vars/</guid>
      <description>List of environment variables to configure the flogo engine
   Environment name Default value Info     FLOGO_LOG_DTFORMAT &amp;ldquo;2006-01-02 15:04:05.000&amp;rdquo; Sets the log date and time format   FLOGO_LOG_LEVEL &amp;ldquo;INFO&amp;rdquo; Sets the log level   FLOGO_RUNNER_TYPE &amp;ldquo;POOLED&amp;rdquo; Sets the type of the runner   FLOGO_RUNNER_WORKERS 5 Sets the number of workers   FLOGO_RUNNER_QUEUE 50 Sets the runner queue size   FLOGO_CONFIG_PATH &amp;ldquo;flogo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with the Web UI</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/getting-started/getting-started-webui/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/getting-started/getting-started-webui/</guid>
      <description>In this document we’ll discuss how to download the Flogo Web UI, a zero-code development environment for IoT and microservices.
Prerequisites Ensure that the following prerequisites have been fulfilled.
Docker Docker is required to pull the Web UI, as it is publicly available via hub.docker.com. If you&amp;rsquo;re running Windows 10, Linux or macOS/OSX then the latest version of Docker should be installed and can be found at the link below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How-to for IOT</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/how-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/how-to/</guid>
      <description>Creating a flogo application is easy andand we&amp;rsquo;ve outlined the steps for you in this howto guide. This guide will walk you through the steps required to create a simple flogo application which can also be used on an IOT device.
Prerequisites Before you can get started building IOT applications with flogo, you need to have the following prerequisites installed:
 The Go programming language should be installed. In order to simplify development and building in Go, we recommend using the gb build tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Configuration Provider</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/extensions-developer/config-provider/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/extensions-developer/config-provider/</guid>
      <description>Unless you want to provide the application configuration (for example: flogo.json) in a different way or format you should not worry about this feature.
We have provided an extension mechanism for you to override the default way of providing the application configuration if needed.
Topics  Default behavior Embedded configuration Custom configuration  Default behavior Out of the box, the default behavior will be as follows:
 Configuration will be passed to the engine in the JSON format Default path for the JSON file will be in the same directory as the application&amp;rsquo;s binary Default name for the JSON file will be &amp;ldquo;flogo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flogo for Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-pi/</guid>
      <description>You can run your Flogo application on a Raspberry Pi device. This documents contains all relevant information on this device including how to build.
Build To build a flogo application for Raspberry Pi, you simply use the build command with the appropriate enviroment variables set.
On mac or linux you execute the following command:
env GOARM=6 GOARCH=arm GOOS=linux flogo build -o  On windows you excute the following commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with the CLI</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/getting-started/getting-started-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/getting-started/getting-started-cli/</guid>
      <description>Flogo provides two different CLIs depending on your needs.
 flogo: This CLI provides app/flow dev support. You can use this to create your applications, build applications, install new extensions, etc. This can also be used in conjunction with your CI/CD pipeline. flogogen: A scafolding CLI used by extensions (activity/trigger) developers to build new extensions.  For additional information, please refer to the README at the flogo-cli repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuously testing Flogo activities</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/extensions-developer/continuously-testing-flogo-activities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/extensions-developer/continuously-testing-flogo-activities/</guid>
      <description>Depending on where you store the source code and how publicly you want to have the code available you have a few options. In this post I&amp;rsquo;ll use Jenkins to show how I can test activities with a local git server and I&amp;rsquo;ll use Travis-CI for activities on GitHub
Intro Before we begin let me quickly walk through my project structure as some of the scripts are based on that structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flogo for Intel Edison</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-edison/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-edison/</guid>
      <description>You can run your Flogo application on a Edison device. This documents contains all relevant information on this device including how to build.
Build To build a flogo application for Edison, you simply use the build command with the appropriate enviroment variables set.
On mac or linux you execute the following command:
env GOARCH=386 GOOS=linux flogo build -o  On windows you excute the following commands:
SET GOARCH=386 SET GOOS=linux flogo build -o  This will compile your application and place the binary in the bin directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flogo for C.H.I.P</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-chip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-chip/</guid>
      <description>You can run your Flogo application on a C.H.I.P. device. This documents contains all relevant information on this device including how to build.
Build To build a flogo application for C.H.I.P., you simply use the build command with the appropriate enviroment variables set.
On mac or linux you execute the following command:
env GOARM=7 GOARCH=arm GOOS=linux flogo build -o  On windows you excute the following commands:
SET GOARM=7 SET GOARCH=arm SET GOOS=linux flogo build -o  This will compile your application and place the binary in the bin directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flogo for BeagleBone</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-beaglebone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-beaglebone/</guid>
      <description>You can run your Flogo application on a BeagleBone device. This documents contains all relevant information on this device including how to build.
Build To build a flogo application for BeagleBone, you simply use the build command with the appropriate enviroment variables set.
On mac or linux you execute the following command:
env GOARM=7 GOARCH=arm GOOS=linux flogo build -o  On windows you excute the following commands:
SET GOARM=7 SET GOARCH=arm SET GOOS=linux flogo build -o  This will compile your application and place the binary in the bin directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building the docs website</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/contributing/contribute-to-docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/contributing/contribute-to-docs/</guid>
      <description>If you want to contribute to the documentation, that is awesome! Your help is very much appreciated, but please do keep in mind the instructions below.
Prerequisites These documentation pages are built with Hugo and we do make some assumptions:
 You have Git 2.5 or greater installed on your machine. You have a GitHub account. Signing up for GitHub is free. You have Hugo installed on your machine.  In Hugo, pages are the core of your site.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>